Guide to the Robert O. Pohl papers, 1973-1998
Pohl, Robert O. papers, 1973-1998
- Series II. Published Reports on Nuclear Waste
  - Regulatory Impact Analysis of Final Environmental Standards for Uranium Mill Tailings at Active Sites, September 1983 (Box 22)
  - Regulatory Impact Analysis of Environmental Standards for Uranium Mill Tailings at Active Sites, March 1983 (Box 22)
  - Office of Nuclear Waste Management Remedial Action (RA) Program (Box 22)
  - Compilation of the Radioactive Waste Disposal Classification System Database, Task 4-Classification of Low Specific Activity Materials, March 1, 1978 (Box 22)
  - Above Ground Gamma Ray Logging for Locating Structures and Areas Containing Elevated Levels of Uranium Decay Chain Radionuclides, April 1978 (Box 22)
  - Draft Supplement to the Final Environmental Statement related to construction and operation of Barnwell Nuclear Fuel Plant, June 1976 (Box 23)
  - Draft Environmental Statement related to operation of Bison Basin Project, June 1980 (Box 23)
  - Draft Environmental Statement related to the operation of the Teton Project, June 1982 (Box 23)
  - Final Environmental Statement related to the decommissioning of the Edgemont Uranium Mill, June 1982 (Box 23)
  - Final Environmental Statement related to the operation of Bison Basin Project, April 1981 (Box 23)
  - Final Environmental Statement related to the operation of Gas Hills Uranium Project, July 1980 (Box 23)
  - Final Environmental Statement related to operation of Lucky McGas Hills Uranium Mill, November 1977 (Box 23)
  - Draft Environmental Statement related to operation of Moab Uranium Mill, November 1977 (Box 23)
  - Draft Environmental Statement related to operation of Lucky Mc Uranium Mill, June 1977 (Box 23)
  - Draft Environmental Statement related to operation of Sweetwater Uranium Project, December 1977 (Box 23)
  - Final Environmental Statement related to operation of Bear Creek Project, June 1977 (Box 23)
  - Draft Environmental Statement related to operation of Bear Creek Project, January 1977 (Box 23)
  - Final Environmental Statement related to operation of Moab Uranium Mill, January 1979 (Box 23)
  - Final Environmental Statement related to operation of White Mesa Uranium Project, May 1979 (Box 23)
  - Final Environmental Statement related to operation of Shootering Canyon Uranium Project, July 1979 (Box 23)
  - Final Environmental Statement related to operation of Split Rock Uranium Mill, February 1980 (Box 23)
  - Draft Environmental Statement related to operation of Plateau Resources Limited, February 1979 (Box 23)
  - Final Environmental Statement related to operation of Irigaray Uranium Solution Mining Project, September 1978 (Box 23)
  - Final Environmental Statement related to operation of Highland Uranium Solution Mining Project, November 1978 (Box 23)
  - Draft Environmental Statement related to operation of White Mesa Uranium Project, December 1978 (Box 23)
  - Draft Environmental Statement related to operation of Gas Hills Uranium Mill, January 1979 (Box 23)
  - Phase II-Title I Engineering Assessment of Inactive Uranium Mill Tailings, Vitro Site, Salt Lake City, Utah, April 30, 1976 (Box 23)
  - Phase II-Title I Engineering Assessment of inactive Uranium Mill Tailings, Mexican Hat Site, Mexican Hat, Utah, March 31, 1977 (Box 23)
  - Draft Environmental Statement related to operation of Split Rock Uranium Mill, November 1978 (Box 23)
  - Draft Environmental Statement related to operation of Morton Ranch Uranium Mill, April 1978 (Box 23)
  - Draft Environmental Statement related to operation of Sand Rock Mill Project, March 1982 (Box 23)
  - Draft Environmental Statement related to the Homestake Mining Company's Pitch Project, July 14, 1978 (Box 23)
- Series III. Correspondence
  - Correspondence, A, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, B, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, C-D, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, E-G, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, H, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, I-K, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, L, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, M-Q, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, R, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, S, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, U-Z, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Letter Book, A, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Letter Book, B, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Letter Book, D, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Letter Book, E-G, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Letter Book, H-J, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Letter Book, K-L, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Letter Book, M, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Letter Book, N-Q, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Letter Book, R, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Letter Book, S, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Letter Book, T-Z, 1972-1974 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence with Cornell Student, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence with Cornell Student, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence with Cornell Student, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Sabbatical, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, A, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, B, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, C-G, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, H, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, I-L, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, M-N, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, O-R, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, S, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, T-Z, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence with Arup, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence with Tom Klitsner, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence with Phil Krasicky, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence with Marie Linvill, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence with Mike Nowak, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence with Marlene Reitz, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence with Mike Skvarla, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Visit to Pohl Institute, Tongji University, May 1988 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Sabbatical, A-G, 1987-1988 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Sabbatical, H-M, 1987-1988 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Sabbatical, N-Z, 1987-1988 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence, A, 1981-1987 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence with Terry Ashworth, 1983-1985 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, B, 1981-1987 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence with Bauerle, 1983-1985 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - APS Meeting, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Buckley Prize Nominations, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, C, 1981-1987 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, D, 1981-1987 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, E, 1983-1987 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence with Eisenmenger, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence with Emin, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, F, 1983-1987 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, G, 1981-1987 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence with Gutfeld (IBM), 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, H, 1980-1987 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, I, 1981-1987 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, K, 1981-1987 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, L, 1980-1987 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, M, 1981-1987 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, N, 1981-1987 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, O, 1982-1987 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, P, 1981-1987 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, R, 1981-1987 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, S, 1984-1987 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, S, 1979-1985 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, T, 1981-1987 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence with Turkes, 1983-1987 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, U, 1982-1985 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, V, 1981-1987 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, W, 1981-1987 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, X-Z, 1983-1987 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, S, 1995-1998 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence with Sahling, 1996-1998 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence with Slack, 1993-1998 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence with Sokolov, 1996-1998 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence with Spiel, 1986-1998 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence with Swartz, 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, T, 1995-1998 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence with Topp, 1995-1998 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, U, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, V, 1995-1998 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence with Veprek, 1990-1998 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, W, 1995-1998 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence with Watson, 1994-1998 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence with White, 1995-1998 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence with Wichert, 1995-1997 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, X-Z, 1995-1997 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, A, 1988-1995 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, B, 1988-1995 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - International Symposium on Boron, Borides, and Related Compounds, 1992-1995 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, B, 1986-1994 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, D, 1989-1993 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, E, 1989-1993 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, F, 1989-1994 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, G, 1976-1994 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, H, 1990-1994 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence with Hessinger, 1993-1995 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, I-K, 1988-1995 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, L, 1982-1995 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence with Liu, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, M, 1989-1995 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, N, 1986-1997 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, O, 1988-1995 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, P, 1988-1992 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, R, 1988-1995 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, S, 1983-1994 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, T, 1987-1994 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, W, 1986-1995 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, X-Z, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, A, 1995-1998 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, B, 1995-1998 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, C, 1995-1998 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence regarding Cryocrystals Conference, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence with Crandall, 1996-1998 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence with Crandall, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, D, 1995-1998 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence with Doyle, 1996-1998 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Deutsche Physikalische Gesellschaft e.V., 1996 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, E, 1995-1998 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence with Enss, 1995-1998 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, F, 1995-1998 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, G, 1994-1998 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, H, 1995-1998 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence with Hessinger, 1995-1997 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, I-J, 1995-1998 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, K, 1994-1998 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, L, 1995-1998 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, M, 1995-1998 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence with Malinovsky, 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence with Medwick, 1996-1998 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence with Meissner, 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, N, 1995-1998 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, O, 1996-1998 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence with Olson, 1995-1998 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Physical Review, 1996-1998 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, P-Q, 1995-1998 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, R, 1995-1998 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence with Ruehle, 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 29)